[{"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Again, it's all a bit pathetic, isn't it?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "I honestly don't know.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "How do you change the culture so that at the very least you can start to put some kind of controls on these types of people legally buying assault weapons and so on?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "They're afraid of a public that wants to have its guns.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "Well, what are they afraid of?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "He just never has on this issue as a national candidate and it's a real defect in him.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Why doesn't he have the balls to do it on something like this?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "ICH: Whom I want or --", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Frank, very quickly, one word or one name, who's your current favorite for VP for Romney?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Well, the most boring is Portman but the second most boring is Pawlenty.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Who's the most likely boring white guy?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Over the past year or so when we introduced mobile payments at Starbucks, we have never seen anything adopted so quickly.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Why is this right for Starbucks?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "That's eventually it.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "That's it?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Well, we believe in simplifying the very complex.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "What's the end game?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "I think it's -- I think it's more added to what you can do.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Why do I need this in my life?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Already 25 percent of all of our customers are using the Starbucks card.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "How many of your customers, do you think, will, say in five years' time, potentially be using Square to buy coffee?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I love -- I love that.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Could that happen?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "I think it -- I wouldn't say that's not possible.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "Why shouldn't it be like that really?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "I'm not here to call the presidency, I appreciate the question.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "I mean what is the -- what is the right call for America?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "We have to give people simple tools that they can define a new reality and a new destiny.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 330, "question": "What is the answer to America incorporated?", "qSentId": 329}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Rather than the cheaper route of making them in the Far East?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "They've done a very good job.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "When you're a new fledgling company like this and it grows so fast, so quickly this kind of issue is going to throw up all kinds of ethical dilemmas that you have to wrestle with, right?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "CHULTZ: I do not.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "Do you tweet?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "I have so much going on in my life that I feel if I add one more thing, I don't have the time.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Why don't you tweet?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I don't put the burden on the American people.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "How much of the problem has been also cultural issues of people just wanting a fast buck, perhaps not wanting to put the graft that their fore bearers put in?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "At all?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "How about America get a grip with its current state of depression and let's discuss that first, because the gun really isn't the problem.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "What is the answer?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "I agree totally with everything you've just said.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "I'm not going to go out and blow somebody up, but why can't we change the way we allow people to buy them?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Why is it the media within a few hours of this latest atrocity of the Sikh temple are able to find out so much information about the shooter.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 442, "question": "Why can't I find out if you're visiting a psychiatrist or a psychologist?", "qSentId": 441}, {"answer": "I completely agree.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Why can't we do that?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "That's the deal, but guess what, unfortunately, the main people who are in charge of this whole process in the country, the first three letters of the constitution, we the people have laid over and played dead.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Where do we meet to make America a better place?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Please don't let me polarize more people.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "What's your thinking on this?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "If we go by diagnosis, it's my 13th year.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How long have you had MS now?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "This is my 13th anniversary with MS, I have been working.", "docId": "120808pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "You're going to be doing this heliboard?", "qSentId": 550}]